{"test_questions": [[{"question": "Referring to the GAL diagram, which is the correct logic function?", "opta": "", "optb": "", "optc": "", "optd": "", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The output of an exclusive-NOR gate is 1. Which input combination is correct?", "opta": "A = 1, B = 0", "optb": "A = 0, B = 1", "optc": "A = 0, B = 0", "optd": "none of the above", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The Boolean SOP expression obtained from the truth table below is ________.", "opta": "", "optb": "", "optc": "", "optd": "None of these", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The 8-input XOR circuit shown has an output of Y = 1. Which input combination below (ordered A \u2013 H) is correct?", "opta": "10111100", "optb": "10111000", "optc": "11100111", "optd": "00011101", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Implementing the expression AB + CDE using NAND logic, we get:", "opta": "(A)", "optb": "(B)", "optc": "(C)", "optd": "(D)", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Before an SOP implementation, the expression  would require a total of how many gates?", "opta": "1", "optb": "2", "optc": "4", "optd": "5", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The following waveform pattern is for a(n) ________.", "opta": "2-input AND gate", "optb": "2-input OR gate", "optc": "Exclusive-OR gate", "optd": "None of the above", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Implementing the expression  with NOR logic, we get:", "opta": "(A)", "optb": "(B)", "optc": "(C)", "optd": "(D)", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A 4-variable AND-OR-Invert circuit produces a 0 at its Y output. Which combination of inputs is correct?", "opta": "", "optb": "", "optc": "", "optd": "none of the above", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The following waveform pattern is for a(n) ________.", "opta": "2-input AND gate", "optb": "2-input OR gate", "optc": "Exclusive-OR gate", "optd": "None of the above", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "To implement the expression , it takes one OR gate and ________.", "opta": "three AND gates and three inverters", "optb": "three AND gates and four inverters", "optc": "three AND gates", "optd": "one AND gate", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "One positive pulse with tw = 75 \u00b5s is applied to one of the inputs of an exclusive-OR circuit. A second positive pulse with tw = 15 \u00b5s is applied to the other input beginning 20 \u00b5s after the leading edge of the first pulse. Which statement describes the output in relation to the inputs?", "opta": "The exclusive-OR output is a 20 s pulse followed by a 40 s pulse, with a separation of 15 s between the pulses.", "optb": "The exclusive-OR output is a 20 s pulse followed by a 15 s pulse, with a separation of 40 s between the pulses.", "optc": "The exclusive-OR output is a 15 s pulse followed by a 40 s pulse.", "optd": "*The exclusive-OR output is a 20 s pulse followed by a 15 s pulse, followed by a 40 s pulse.", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "How many AND gates are required to implement the Boolean expression, ?", "opta": "1", "optb": "2", "optc": "3", "optd": "4", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "How many NOT gates are required to implement the Boolean expression, ?", "opta": "1", "optb": "2", "optc": "4", "optd": "5", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The inverter can be produced with how many NAND gates?", "opta": "1", "optb": "2", "optc": "3", "optd": "4", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A 4-variable AND-OR circuit produces a 0 at its Y output. Which combination of inputs is correct?", "opta": "A = 0, B = 0, C = 1, D = 1", "optb": "A = 1, B = 1, C = 0, D = 0", "optc": "A = 1, B = 1, C = 1, D = 1", "optd": "A = 1, B = 0, C = 1, D = 0", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A 4-variable AND-OR circuit produces a 1 at its Y output. Which combination of inputs is correct?", "opta": "A = 0, B = 0, C = 0, D = 0", "optb": "A = 0, B = 1, C = 1, D = 0", "optc": "A = 1, B = 1, C = 0, D = 0", "optd": "A = 1, B = 0, C = 0, D = 0", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Implementing the expression  using NAND logic, we get:", "opta": "(A)", "optb": "(B)", "optc": "(C)", "optd": "(D)", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Implementing the expression  using NAND logic, we get:", "opta": "(A)", "optb": "(B)", "optc": "(C)", "optd": "(D)", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The following waveform pattern is for a(n) ________.", "opta": "2-input AND gate", "optb": "2-input OR gate", "optc": "Exclusive-OR gate", "optd": "None of the above", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Implementation of the Boolean expression  results in ________.", "opta": "three AND gates, one OR gate", "optb": "three AND gates, one NOT gate, one OR gate", "optc": "three AND gates, one NOT gate, three OR gates", "optd": "three AND gates, three OR gates", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "One possible output expression for an AND-OR-Invert circuit having one AND gate with inputs A, B, and C and one AND gate with inputs D and E is ________.", "opta": "", "optb": "", "optc": "", "optd": "", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "How many 2-input NOR gates does it take to produce a 2-input NAND gate?", "opta": "1", "optb": "2", "optc": "3", "optd": "4", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A logic circuit with an output  consists of ________.", "opta": "two AND gates, two OR gates, two inverters", "optb": "three AND gates, two OR gates, one inverter", "optc": "two AND gates, one OR gate, two inverters", "optd": "two AND gates, one OR gate", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}]]}